mio.co.za 2004-06-07

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Thank you for viewing the information on these sites and for providing us with information about yourself. 

To make sure that there are no misunderstandings which could lead to possible disputes about your online dealings with us, it is important that you read and understand the following disclaimer which covers all interactions and transactions on these sites. 

**DISCLAIMER**

  * The information appearing on these pages is made available without any representation or warranty whatsoever, whether express or implied, and no liability will attach to   MIO or Prefix Technologies  in this regard. 
  * All information regarding the products and services, including information about their terms and conditions, and prices is subject to change without notice. You should check, by enquiry at  [pinfo@prefix.co.za](mailto:pinfo@prefix.co.za) or [info@mio.co.za](mailto:info@mio.co.za) that the prices quoted and information presented  on these pages are correct 
  *  Neither MIO nor Prefix Technologies accepts liability for any loss, whether direct, indirect , consequential or any loss arising from information made available on these pages and actions or transactions resulting therefrom. 
  *  MIO and Prefix Technologies’ Products and Services are only available in the Republic of South Africa unless specifically stated otherwise. 
  * The laws of the Republic of South Africa will govern all terms and conditions, of any products and services, contained in these pages. If you apply for any products or services through our Internet sites, you also consent to the terms and conditions of such products and services and submit to the jurisdiction of the South African courts in regard to all proceedings, actions, applications or the like instituted by either party against the other, and in any way arising from any stated terms and conditions. 

By registering your information with us and/or applying for any products and services offered on these Internet sites, you agree to this disclaimer. 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

MIO Entertainment, the owners of Music Industry Online ([www.mio.co.za](http://www.mio.co.za/)), is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from our users. Please read the following to understand our views and practices regarding personal information, and how they pertain to you as you use our various features and services. This statement discloses the current privacy practices for our Web site. If we make any substantive changes to this policy, we'll announce it on our sites. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us on [info@mio.co.za](mailto:info@mio.co.za)

**This Privacy Statement answers the following questions:**

  * What information does MIO Entertainment gather about you?   

  * How does MIO Entertainment use your personal information?   

  * Will MIO Entertainment disclose any of your personal information?   

  * What kind of security measures do we take to protect your information from accidental loss or disclosure?   

  * How can you deactivate your account or correct or revise information that we have about you?   

  * How will you know if MIO Entertainment's privacy policy has changed?   

  * What Else Should You Know About Your Privacy?   

  * What Information Does MIO Entertainment Gather About You?

**What information does MIO Entertainment gather about you?**

MIO Entertainment collects a limited amount of information about our readers, so that we can provide a site that is more interesting and useful, as well as provide advertising that is more appropriate for our readers. We ask for your name, email address, and other personal information when you register to use our forums or if you sign up for any special or personalized service such as a subscription service. We also may ask for such information at other times, such as whenever you enter competitions or other promotions sponsored by MIO Entertainment and/or our partners. Sometimes we conduct surveys, too, although you don't have to respond to them.

We also collect IP addresses to help us understand how our audience uses our site, so that we can make our site better and improve our users' overall experience when they visit MIO Entertainment. For these same reasons, if your browser is set up to accept them, we use a feature known as a "cookie." Cookies contain bits of information that Web sites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site such as ours. Although we may assign your browser a cookie, it doesn't tell us who you are. Only you can do that.

**How Does MIO Entertainment Use Your Personal Information?**

MIO Entertainment collects personal information to provide you, the user, with the best and most personalised Web experience possible and to provide our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience. In short, by knowing a little about you, MIO Entertainment can deliver more relevant content and advertisements to you while at our Web site. And it's free.   
MIO Entertainment conducts research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour based on the information you provide us when you register, participate in a contest or other promotion on our site, or from our server log files. This research is compiled and analysed only on an aggregated basis. We do this to better understand our users and improve your overall experience when using our service. 

Sometimes we ask for personal information when providing special, personalised service. If you don't want to give us that information, you certainly don't have to, but you may not be able to take advantage of certain products or services. For example, we can't send you a prize if you do not supply us with a delivery address.

**Will MIO Entertainment Disclose Any of Your Personal Information?**

MIO Entertainment will not disclose any information about individual users, except as described in this Privacy Statement, or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of MIO Entertainment. 

We do not give, rent, lend, or sell individual information to our advertisers, only aggregate information. For example, we might tell advertisers that there are 5,000 subscribers to one of our newsletters, but we won't tell them that Joe Bloggs is one of them, and we won't tell them that his email address is joeblogs@mywebaddy.co.za. We may also use this aggregated information to help the advertisers reach the kind of audience they want. In this process, the advertiser never has access to individual account information. Only MIO Entertainment has access to individuals' accounts. 

We may also disclose aggregate information (for example, 10, 000 of our readers clicked on a message board advertisement last month) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

We may disclose personal information in some limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, such as in the rules of a sweepstakes or some new service. For example, if we're going to give personal information to the sponsor of a contest, we'll tell you that before you sign up for the contest, so that you can decide whether or not to enter. 

**What Kind of Security Measures Do We Take to Protect Your Information from Accidental Loss or Disclosure?**

MIO Entertainment is committed to protecting your personal information. All information that you provide to us is stored on secure servers. 

Personalised areas of our sites, such as the MIO Entertainment Forums are password-protected. Only you have access to these password-protected areas. We recommend that you do not share your passwords with anyone. MIO Entertainment will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also if you are using a computer that others have access to such as one in a computer lab, Internet café or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving our site. 

**Will MIO Entertainment Use Your Information for Direct Mailings?**

If you register with MIO Entertainment or sign up for any our personalized services, we will email you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may interest you. Only MIO Entertainment (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these emails. If you do not want to receive such offers and mailings, you can let us know on [info@mio.co.za](mailto:info@mio.co.za)

**How Can You Edit the Information We Have About You?**  
If you want to correct or change the information in your Forum Profile, or any other information we have about you, please go to  
<http://www.mio.co.za/forums/>  
If you want to change your email address for our mailing lists, please click the link below. You will need to unsubscribe to all email with your old address, and then re-subscribe with your new one.  
<http://www.mio.co.za/subscribe>

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

MIO Entertainment may make changes to this Privacy Statement at any time, but we'll notify you of any substantive or material change (by way of email) and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out. 

**What Else Should You Know About Your Privacy?**

The information you post on forums and discussion lists is visible to the public. Please remember that whenever you disclose personal information publicly - for example, on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. If you don't want strangers to send you email, don't post your email address on a message board. 

Furthermore, while we do our best to protect your personal information, MIO Entertainment can not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. What does all this mean? Just as in the music world, you must protect yourself. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. Many of our advertisers or partners link from our site to areas on their own sites where they sell their own goods and services. If you follow these links from our site to theirs, you should be aware that these other sites have their privacy and data collection practices.MIO Entertainment has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. For more information regarding a site and its privacy policies, check that site.

Please direct any queries to [info@mio.co.za](mailto:info@mio.co.za)
